[{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f14"},"rt":12374,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85926,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f15"},"rt":17504,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":103505,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f16"},"rt":32708,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136288,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f17"},"rt":12413,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148786,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f18"},"rt":38364,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":187225,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"K O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f1a"},"rt":8708,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":201511,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f1b"},"rt":23625,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225218,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f1c"},"rt":27745,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253047,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f1d"},"rt":41019,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":294144,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X X J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f1e"},"rt":27248,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321470,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f1f"},"rt":13852,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335382,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f20"},"rt":9322,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344842,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f21"},"rt":18568,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":363480,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f22"},"rt":15036,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378591,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f23"},"rt":11064,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389719,"subject":"G8EED","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"62961a6c19ab6d19ba4bc4d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f35"},"rt":8237,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":56328,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f36"},"rt":8462,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64963,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f37"},"rt":18549,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83642,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f38"},"rt":21080,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104827,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f39"},"rt":83279,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":188255,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"O I O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PMI 04 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f3b"},"rt":9966,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":203267,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f3c"},"rt":12992,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216356,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f3d"},"rt":21453,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237908,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f3e"},"rt":16303,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":254312,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AM12 PMJ I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f3f"},"rt":24577,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278988,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B B F X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f40"},"rt":10117,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289203,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f41"},"rt":7935,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297237,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f42"},"rt":29362,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":326763,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"C L Z X 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f43"},"rt":42872,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369734,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f44"},"rt":47920,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417803,"subject":"POHH4","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM02 PM02 PMB B B B F C F F F B B J J M X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f56"},"rt":20609,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":107486,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f57"},"rt":11744,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119305,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f58"},"rt":19402,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138775,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f59"},"rt":34095,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172952,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U Z A A O O Z Z U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f5a"},"rt":66043,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239080,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I 04 PM03 PM11 AM03 PM04 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f5c"},"rt":7531,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275569,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f5d"},"rt":12306,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287948,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f5e"},"rt":44735,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332758,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B I I B B B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f5f"},"rt":11709,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":344538,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f60"},"rt":40732,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385342,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M Z G P O F F F F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f61"},"rt":20980,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406497,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f62"},"rt":7012,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413584,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f63"},"rt":25052,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":438721,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f64"},"rt":11168,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449967,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f65"},"rt":25863,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":475897,"subject":"6JRLV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"61044034c10d38548dce50dd","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f77"},"rt":18930,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75827,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"610 AM11 AMA 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f78"},"rt":10404,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86314,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f79"},"rt":49047,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135434,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O C A U C C A C C C A 05 PM06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f7a"},"rt":16567,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152086,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A Z 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PME E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f7b"},"rt":19275,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":171422,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AM12 PMF F I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f7d"},"rt":12003,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":191814,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f7e"},"rt":22294,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215303,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f7f"},"rt":19137,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234519,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,M","hovered":"E 7B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f80"},"rt":22264,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256858,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"J J M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f81"},"rt":9917,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268283,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f82"},"rt":11629,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279988,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f83"},"rt":8070,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288143,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f84"},"rt":35501,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":325491,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":"F H H L Z Z Z Z Z Z L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f85"},"rt":32091,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357671,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":"03 PMI I 12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f86"},"rt":20901,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378638,"subject":"3P3K0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6127c369bdff7dc17f0724a2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X C 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f98"},"rt":15234,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":59758,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"Z 12 PM11 AMA C 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f99"},"rt":7186,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":67077,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8E E 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f9a"},"rt":28188,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":95424,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H 4C A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f9b"},"rt":71222,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166793,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM01 PMU U G G O K A 04 PMH A A A H H H H H 01 PM12 PM01 PM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AMA A 11 AM11 AMA A U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f9c"},"rt":49968,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":217123,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"6I I O 11 AMI I O O 01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM06 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f9e"},"rt":6796,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":227330,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"0E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320f9f"},"rt":45400,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272871,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C I 09 AM09 AMB B B B 12 PMM 01 PMX X X I B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa0"},"rt":24638,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297656,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa1"},"rt":13461,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":311300,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa2"},"rt":19456,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332007,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F E E E E F F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa3"},"rt":8162,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343565,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PMF F F B B B F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa4"},"rt":3627,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347340,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa5"},"rt":12437,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359917,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"6Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa6"},"rt":6784,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366814,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fa7"},"rt":18652,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392547,"subject":"H03VL","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f84dfd00f8a7b1bacf4f3e3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fb9"},"rt":28416,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":102637,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A A 11 AMA A U 12 PM12 PMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fba"},"rt":12323,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115015,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"11 AM01 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fbb"},"rt":8309,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123374,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fbc"},"rt":5966,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129388,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fbd"},"rt":17417,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146856,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"66O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fbf"},"rt":11202,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":163607,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc0"},"rt":43982,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207641,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"42M 12 PMM M H H M J 10 AMF F F B B X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc1"},"rt":46437,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":254133,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B I I K K F 10 AMJ A G A A 10 AMF B G 5G B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc2"},"rt":29270,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":283449,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"3J J J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc3"},"rt":8076,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291584,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4J F B B 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc4"},"rt":9935,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301568,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc5"},"rt":9276,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310898,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F M M G G B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc6"},"rt":10733,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":321682,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O L 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc7"},"rt":8670,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330407,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fc8"},"rt":10311,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340766,"subject":"YT40Q","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"59278c090220760001fda664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fda"},"rt":24374,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":72278,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fdb"},"rt":16930,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89260,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fdc"},"rt":14903,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104210,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fdd"},"rt":9979,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":114243,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"U 04 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fde"},"rt":19046,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133343,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PMA I I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe0"},"rt":5712,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":141680,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe1"},"rt":15688,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157410,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F M X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe2"},"rt":19789,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177243,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe3"},"rt":24775,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202060,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"08 AMB B M B 10 AM10 AMJ 11 AME B M 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe4"},"rt":5688,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207793,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"001 PME B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe5"},"rt":5922,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213760,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe6"},"rt":7436,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221242,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe7"},"rt":10898,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":232193,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe8"},"rt":7956,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240193,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AM10 AM01 PM02 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fe9"},"rt":10220,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250461,"subject":"E0UF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5fe45e3b520dd11baee55be3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"302 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320ffb"},"rt":89634,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166975,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM08 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320ffc"},"rt":6104,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173743,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320ffd"},"rt":9912,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183815,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320ffe"},"rt":6406,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":190379,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86320fff"},"rt":11608,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":202145,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321001"},"rt":14607,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":222870,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321002"},"rt":24550,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247601,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321003"},"rt":33293,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281055,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321004"},"rt":48579,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":329794,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321005"},"rt":9285,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339377,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321006"},"rt":10901,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350437,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321007"},"rt":16349,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366944,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321008"},"rt":17078,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":384178,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321009"},"rt":11043,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395379,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632100a"},"rt":8910,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":404446,"subject":"XVGF9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f80bc3c445c6a13cd7c4fb5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632101c"},"rt":18458,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71495,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632101d"},"rt":114874,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186488,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A O O O O I O D D J D D D K D D D K K Z E E K K D D D K F 12 PMD Z Z Z K G D K 12 PM12 PMK Z Z 04 PM12 PMA A 10 AM10 AM12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632101e"},"rt":15003,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":201849,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632101f"},"rt":25141,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227096,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"O U 01 PM01 PMZ Z 03 PM04 PMH F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321020"},"rt":72360,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":299570,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,Z","hovered":"I I 03 PMF O O O O A A 12 PM12 PMA A C I 03 PMO O O O A A O O A A O O O Z Z O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321022"},"rt":10282,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313427,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321023"},"rt":45734,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359277,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"3C C C H M M M B B B F B Z X 01 PMX 01 PMX O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321024"},"rt":47000,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406390,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E E B B B B F F F G X X M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321025"},"rt":46622,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":453124,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"I I E F B F B B B B M M M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321026"},"rt":14693,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467929,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321027"},"rt":12215,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480262,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"I M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321028"},"rt":9203,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":489588,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321029"},"rt":16545,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506240,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3J X Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632102a"},"rt":6700,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":513057,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632102b"},"rt":25640,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538803,"subject":"XWK1T","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"602f329284781fbf09e0cafc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"3J M 02 PMX X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632103d"},"rt":35465,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":101825,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"009 AM11 AM11 AM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632103e"},"rt":8051,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109990,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632103f"},"rt":10550,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120944,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321040"},"rt":6822,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127874,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"704 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321041"},"rt":20828,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148879,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321043"},"rt":9695,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":162308,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321044"},"rt":39745,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202162,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321045"},"rt":43751,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246021,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321046"},"rt":40454,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":286584,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321047"},"rt":9004,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295695,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321048"},"rt":9291,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305091,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"612 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321049"},"rt":8434,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313650,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632104a"},"rt":8658,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":322417,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632104b"},"rt":6822,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329360,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632104c"},"rt":12727,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342189,"subject":"2BW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"608a3af1093571af0fb3bc58","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632105e"},"rt":46114,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99844,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AMF 11 AMF 01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AMF F 11 AM11 AMF F Z 09 AM08 AM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632105f"},"rt":16467,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116428,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A Z K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321060"},"rt":26705,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":143269,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O A C C C C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321061"},"rt":12862,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":156243,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321062"},"rt":26865,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183231,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321064"},"rt":11842,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":198405,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321065"},"rt":26993,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225527,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"5F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321066"},"rt":13821,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239461,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":"L L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321067"},"rt":3326,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":242911,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321068"},"rt":1902,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244928,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321069"},"rt":12645,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257695,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632106a"},"rt":17364,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":275170,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632106b"},"rt":6993,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":282279,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632106c"},"rt":2818,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285217,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632106d"},"rt":1979,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287312,"subject":"85RQA","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63041730eb834af159486dfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632107f"},"rt":67768,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":197747,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"04 PM10 AM11 AMA A A A A A A 02 PMO 11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM06 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMF 02 PM01 PM12 PMF 11 AM11 AM10 AMA 11 AMZ F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321080"},"rt":27126,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226168,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"01 PM02 PM07 PMK E D 12 PMD D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321081"},"rt":20495,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246865,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F Z 11 AM11 AMC C C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321082"},"rt":9133,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":256090,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"11 AM12 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321083"},"rt":123658,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":379882,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I 08 AM08 AM03 PM03 PM03 PMI C 09 AMO O 12 PM12 PMI F F 02 PM03 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMZ A A O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321085"},"rt":11878,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":397314,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321086"},"rt":56844,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454345,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"09 AM10 AMC B I B B B B B 10 AMB B B B 09 AM10 AMB 12 PM01 PM02 PMO X 01 PMX O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321087"},"rt":58052,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":512676,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"Z B 11 AM11 AMF F F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321088"},"rt":58528,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":571483,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I E J E E E 02 PMM M J J 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321089"},"rt":18815,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590416,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H P 02 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632108a"},"rt":24787,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":615420,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM 02 PM01 PM12 PML L E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632108b"},"rt":16479,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":631983,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AMB G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632108c"},"rt":17991,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":650078,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"I 04 PMZ Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632108d"},"rt":11177,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661382,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632108e"},"rt":22715,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":684277,"subject":"456UX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5962e5c8ba58f30001d48048","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a0"},"rt":27903,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94351,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"608 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A A A A O O O 4554532"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a1"},"rt":14745,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109155,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PMD D E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a2"},"rt":58055,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167266,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C C 12 PM12 PM12 PM06 PMO 12 PM04 PM01 PMK K C C A A C C 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a3"},"rt":21622,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":188943,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PMH A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a4"},"rt":35267,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":224263,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"7I U O I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a6"},"rt":6743,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":239681,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM456"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a7"},"rt":18828,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258584,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a8"},"rt":93185,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351819,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G B F F F F F F F B B B B B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210a9"},"rt":58061,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":410040,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J B B B B B B B M 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210aa"},"rt":20221,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430311,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F 02 PM01 PM12 PM02 PMF 02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ab"},"rt":56889,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487262,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ac"},"rt":13601,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500922,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F B B F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ad"},"rt":22522,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":523497,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J 02 PM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ae"},"rt":15973,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":539527,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210af"},"rt":19068,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558670,"subject":"PMVJO","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"629e202465d7385d50c7287b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X X X X X 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c1"},"rt":25695,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":68129,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c2"},"rt":10570,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78793,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c3"},"rt":8398,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":87287,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"211 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c4"},"rt":7811,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":95195,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"C 04 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c5"},"rt":16437,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111741,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c7"},"rt":7782,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":123334,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c8"},"rt":25854,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":149283,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I B B B B B B B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210c9"},"rt":34317,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183691,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ca"},"rt":25161,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":208949,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210cb"},"rt":8721,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217761,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210cc"},"rt":7882,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225735,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210cd"},"rt":6759,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232591,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ce"},"rt":18977,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":251665,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O F O N M Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210cf"},"rt":6838,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258609,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210d0"},"rt":10201,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268901,"subject":"2UXF2","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e2"},"rt":14081,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":711725,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C C 01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e3"},"rt":11389,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":723220,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e4"},"rt":8955,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":732288,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e5"},"rt":5827,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":738196,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e6"},"rt":6551,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":744872,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e8"},"rt":4632,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":752295,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210e9"},"rt":42775,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":795194,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ea"},"rt":2743,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":798076,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210eb"},"rt":2135,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":800292,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ec"},"rt":3352,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":803752,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ed"},"rt":2193,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":806024,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ee"},"rt":3602,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":809700,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210ef"},"rt":5943,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":815765,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210f0"},"rt":4698,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":820575,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863210f1"},"rt":58199,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":878851,"subject":"9ZCS8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60e28114f6eac9b665ff15d2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321103"},"rt":63424,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":626732,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321104"},"rt":8649,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":635636,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321105"},"rt":22732,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":658567,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321106"},"rt":11254,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":670028,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321107"},"rt":55861,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":726161,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321109"},"rt":10824,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":742715,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632110a"},"rt":22078,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":764992,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632110b"},"rt":65060,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":830257,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632110c"},"rt":10421,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":840909,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632110d"},"rt":8946,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":850064,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632110e"},"rt":8623,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":858887,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632110f"},"rt":13591,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":872677,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321110"},"rt":18560,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":891445,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321111"},"rt":20474,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":912234,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321112"},"rt":8776,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":921213,"subject":"SQMR7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c671f12a26a8500014431e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321124"},"rt":53535,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":126773,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM11 AMA 12 PMK A A 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321125"},"rt":12447,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139367,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"K K 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321126"},"rt":11858,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151324,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AMC C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321127"},"rt":9641,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161131,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321128"},"rt":8484,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169754,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632112a"},"rt":10436,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":184287,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM09 AMM 6E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632112b"},"rt":19501,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203863,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"X X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632112c"},"rt":30021,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234025,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B B F F G C C C C G F C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632112d"},"rt":36408,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270500,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I B B B M M I I J J J I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632112e"},"rt":9135,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279711,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632112f"},"rt":9658,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289435,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"6M 12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321130"},"rt":39433,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328987,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321131"},"rt":22783,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359863,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"I B O C C X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321132"},"rt":6744,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367006,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321133"},"rt":14037,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381310,"subject":"Z01BX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321145"},"rt":136963,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":232429,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA 11 AM11 AM11 AMF K O A 11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMC A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321146"},"rt":37129,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":270001,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"O 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321147"},"rt":77268,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":347382,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321148"},"rt":128568,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":476227,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321149"},"rt":201784,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":678320,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632114b"},"rt":26238,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":712055,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12 PM10 AMJ M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632114c"},"rt":19695,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":731863,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632114d"},"rt":138999,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":870965,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F F X X 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632114e"},"rt":103986,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":975260,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AMJ J I J I J J E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632114f"},"rt":23417,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":998943,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321150"},"rt":51145,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1050211,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321151"},"rt":31452,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1081780,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321152"},"rt":127477,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1209365,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"M 11 AMJ F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321153"},"rt":10758,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1220392,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321154"},"rt":88783,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1309283,"subject":"2F1HW","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"6105a358dfef036828f7d2fa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"12 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMM M M M J J 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321166"},"rt":15215,"condition":"211","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75824,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321167"},"rt":14419,"condition":"211","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90567,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321168"},"rt":11884,"condition":"211","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":102729,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"2C A Z Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321169"},"rt":42021,"condition":"211","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145053,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"U H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632116a"},"rt":53509,"condition":"211","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199359,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O I I I O O O I O O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632116c"},"rt":32211,"condition":"211","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":237658,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"000J E E E I 01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM10 AMG C O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632116d"},"rt":43108,"condition":"211","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280853,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J F O O X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632116e"},"rt":48504,"condition":"211","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329428,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B B B B B B F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632116f"},"rt":23832,"condition":"211","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":355169,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321170"},"rt":25458,"condition":"211","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380721,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F 3C C C C X F I 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321171"},"rt":11714,"condition":"211","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392494,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"2M L M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321172"},"rt":18346,"condition":"211","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410904,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F B G C G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321173"},"rt":16306,"condition":"211","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427285,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"L B H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321174"},"rt":6257,"condition":"211","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":433613,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PM03 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321175"},"rt":13088,"condition":"211","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446782,"subject":"MRZ30","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305646d20b66a6b9d44425f","sona_id":"5f7654f879a4420e6d20971b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321187"},"rt":47490,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208566,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AMF 11 AM11 AMZ 12 PM12 PM02 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321188"},"rt":20868,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":229479,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321189"},"rt":12624,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":242150,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632118a"},"rt":12776,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":254975,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"01 PM02 PM04 PMH H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632118b"},"rt":14141,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":269168,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632118d"},"rt":11283,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":283230,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632118e"},"rt":30043,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313320,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"B B B B B X O M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632118f"},"rt":48833,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362199,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"1C 10 AM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321190"},"rt":45300,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":407545,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"09 AMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321191"},"rt":8362,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415955,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321192"},"rt":10531,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426536,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321193"},"rt":12215,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438791,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B F 10 AMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321194"},"rt":14335,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":453179,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321195"},"rt":6490,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459738,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321196"},"rt":7198,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466983,"subject":"0LJCD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211a8"},"rt":51460,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120280,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211a9"},"rt":8812,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129154,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211aa"},"rt":21452,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":150669,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C C 06 PM07 PM08 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ab"},"rt":19344,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170069,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"08 AM02 PM03 PM04 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMH A A 10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ac"},"rt":16269,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186394,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C U A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ae"},"rt":18963,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":208510,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"04 PM03 PMM 08 AMJ E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211af"},"rt":15910,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224471,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b0"},"rt":25219,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249737,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2J J X C C G 6A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b1"},"rt":52715,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":302504,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E 02 PM01 PM12 PMB 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b2"},"rt":6918,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":309469,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b3"},"rt":7159,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":316675,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b4"},"rt":6662,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323386,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b5"},"rt":15565,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":338995,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AMX N 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b6"},"rt":8909,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347955,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AM03 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211b7"},"rt":31933,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379940,"subject":"FZ00G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5c61a77464fd2100010e09f7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"J B 05 PM03 PMX X C C K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211c9"},"rt":59040,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133176,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ca"},"rt":16106,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149382,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D 5D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211cb"},"rt":21284,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170764,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211cc"},"rt":14485,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185343,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211cd"},"rt":47752,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":233190,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"5I A A A I O 08 AMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211cf"},"rt":8673,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":252521,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d0"},"rt":54336,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306950,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"08 AM09 AM01 PMX O 12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMX X O X Z N 01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d1"},"rt":62939,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369983,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B X X B X X X B F F G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d2"},"rt":60404,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":430684,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I B I 3B B I 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d3"},"rt":17088,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448071,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2F M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d4"},"rt":12790,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460962,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d5"},"rt":11685,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472742,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d6"},"rt":12351,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":485187,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d7"},"rt":8878,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":494160,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PM03 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211d8"},"rt":25725,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":519980,"subject":"ZVW5L","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630486d3135ebae69cf08f0d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMK X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ea"},"rt":396477,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":470467,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"12 PM12 PMA 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211eb"},"rt":12740,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":483333,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ec"},"rt":13992,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":497385,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ed"},"rt":59412,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":556858,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"206 PM06 PM05 PMD 04 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211ee"},"rt":108032,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":664939,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"04 PM05 PMI I 09 AM10 AM06 PMK A A A C F F A A A F A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f0"},"rt":60399,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":737530,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"M I J F M M M B B F F C C G O O K A K K H H G G G G G G G C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f1"},"rt":30702,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":768386,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f2"},"rt":48022,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":816473,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"G B B O O G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f3"},"rt":46654,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":863193,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"M 01 PMM J J J J B B B B M M J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f4"},"rt":45346,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":908601,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f5"},"rt":28994,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":937673,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PML L M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f6"},"rt":25281,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":963017,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B B B F B B 09 AM10 AMF G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f7"},"rt":17002,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":980081,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f8"},"rt":28785,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1008929,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"11 AM05 PM06 PM04 PM03 PMX 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863211f9"},"rt":30204,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1039193,"subject":"E3DH7","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5f4ddfb46cc10eaac964361a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632120b"},"rt":34028,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169334,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMC C 10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632120c"},"rt":12691,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":182114,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632120d"},"rt":90143,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":272348,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C I A 02 PM01 PMZ Z F 10 AMC C K F F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632120e"},"rt":61302,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":333885,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U Z A A F 01 PMZ Z 01 PM01 PM01 PMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632120f"},"rt":126787,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":460909,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"03 PMH U U G K F H H H K K K F O O O 03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMI O 09 AM08 AMZ U U 03 PM03 PMZ A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321211"},"rt":55745,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":521048,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E F F G C C O O E G C C L H H A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321212"},"rt":63452,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":584580,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321213"},"rt":81176,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665985,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B B F F F F F G B G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321214"},"rt":32978,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":699759,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321215"},"rt":10249,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":710083,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321216"},"rt":9074,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":719244,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321217"},"rt":13223,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":732563,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321218"},"rt":32690,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":765335,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B O Z Z Z H Z Z N N Z Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321219"},"rt":8281,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":773693,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632121a"},"rt":43969,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":817738,"subject":"AYAAZ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"60b800d2c81484710290317a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X 02 PMK J H 07 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632122c"},"rt":40100,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109872,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AMX X X X F U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632122d"},"rt":8726,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":118660,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"H H D K K K D K K O 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632122e"},"rt":7796,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":126509,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632122f"},"rt":9924,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136487,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321230"},"rt":77874,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":214412,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I I A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321232"},"rt":13895,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":234745,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E I I I E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321233"},"rt":23721,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258522,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"O X O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321234"},"rt":66814,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325392,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B X X X F C C G E E G C C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321235"},"rt":115737,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":441267,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I E F B B E B B F F B B F F E E F F B B I I E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321236"},"rt":7664,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449045,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F F E F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321237"},"rt":9093,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458181,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321238"},"rt":6700,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464933,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321239"},"rt":12717,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":477702,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632123a"},"rt":7188,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":484939,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632123b"},"rt":19268,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504257,"subject":"WE2OF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615a91510a1a37d8c1a1ca7a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"J 02 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632124d"},"rt":24731,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":294171,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C 12 PM12 PM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632124e"},"rt":30446,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":324683,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM12 PMK 05 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632124f"},"rt":12927,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":337678,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321250"},"rt":25237,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":362979,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"11 AM02 PM03 PM04 PMH A A A H 04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMB B 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321251"},"rt":88687,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":451750,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O 0I I I I I I I I 10 AMA 01 PMA A A A I I A 10 AM08 AM02 PM03 PM02 PMZ I 03 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321253"},"rt":19890,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":476582,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321254"},"rt":20058,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496706,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"12 PM4C C F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321255"},"rt":86701,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583476,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"09 AM09 AMB B X X X X X X C F 02 PM10 AMG G A K K K K G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321256"},"rt":290395,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":874374,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J E B B 10 AMI E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321257"},"rt":10557,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":885312,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321258"},"rt":8532,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":893912,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMM L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321259"},"rt":74408,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":968389,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F 10 AMG F 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632125a"},"rt":93616,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1062395,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"10 AMB B B B Z N 06 PM06 PMZ Z N N N Z H Z B H Z N N 02 PM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632125b"},"rt":11417,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1074304,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PMX 03 PM03 PMX X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632125c"},"rt":21345,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1095714,"subject":"9AWT0","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"614d673e3a5fd5cb2b5b6eb7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMC C 02 PMX X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632126e"},"rt":13869,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":36510,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632126f"},"rt":13391,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":49996,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321270"},"rt":10713,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":60800,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321271"},"rt":7419,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":68317,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"05 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321272"},"rt":6600,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75012,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321274"},"rt":5172,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":83006,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12 PM11 AM7E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321275"},"rt":16518,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99624,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F 5C C C F F F O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321276"},"rt":47537,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147256,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G G F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321277"},"rt":11886,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":159246,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321278"},"rt":8333,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167678,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"M B F 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321279"},"rt":6608,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174376,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"201 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632127a"},"rt":9180,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183650,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F B 10 AMB G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632127b"},"rt":8820,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":192568,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632127c"},"rt":10053,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202716,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"E X 01 PM03 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632127d"},"rt":8854,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211670,"subject":"7XFWB","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"6168aed54402a254c7926b1f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"112 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PMX X 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632128f"},"rt":15377,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123738,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321290"},"rt":32999,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":156761,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321291"},"rt":16485,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173280,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321292"},"rt":33119,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206430,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F","hovered":"01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321293"},"rt":43548,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":250000,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I O O A A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321295"},"rt":23964,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275435,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"A I I 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321296"},"rt":29521,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304992,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"E E I I I I E B B A B B B B C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321297"},"rt":125715,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430734,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"B B B 10 AM01 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321298"},"rt":19604,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":450398,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321299"},"rt":16235,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466661,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632129a"},"rt":13215,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":479907,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632129b"},"rt":344695,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":824627,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632129c"},"rt":11827,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":836517,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632129d"},"rt":111503,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":948047,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632129e"},"rt":59811,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1007918,"subject":"DG6N8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f558a5eb6604495cc52268d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b0"},"rt":60178,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":156762,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"11 AM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b1"},"rt":38480,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":195369,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM03 PMD K 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b2"},"rt":59833,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":255245,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U,E","hovered":"11 AM11 AMC 02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b3"},"rt":125106,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":380389,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PM12 PMK K K K 06 PM05 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMH H 02 PM04 PMH H H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b4"},"rt":112643,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":493155,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"12 PMI O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b6"},"rt":22017,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":520069,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"04 PMF G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b7"},"rt":117469,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":637577,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F Z 09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b8"},"rt":48208,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":685933,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"G B 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212b9"},"rt":34130,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":720101,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"12 PM09 AMJ J J 008 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212ba"},"rt":40491,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":760626,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212bb"},"rt":17346,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":778011,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM12 PM12 PMM M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212bc"},"rt":14322,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":792379,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"08 AM02 PMM M B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212bd"},"rt":24457,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":816873,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"11 AM06 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212be"},"rt":30154,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":847067,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"10 AM11 AM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212bf"},"rt":38351,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":885455,"subject":"CG79Z","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"61120b45c48a14ebaae1e5b2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"12 PM02 PM02 PMF F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d1"},"rt":10285,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":39032,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM10 AM10 AMK F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d2"},"rt":7362,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":46471,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"5D 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d3"},"rt":13675,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":60204,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"2C C C 11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d4"},"rt":5051,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":65327,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d5"},"rt":6088,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71487,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d7"},"rt":10466,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":83756,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"008 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMG G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d8"},"rt":11627,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":95448,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212d9"},"rt":20089,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115603,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212da"},"rt":21108,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":136788,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I E I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212db"},"rt":7256,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144114,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212dc"},"rt":9406,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153581,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212dd"},"rt":10803,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164449,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212de"},"rt":8583,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":173095,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212df"},"rt":7550,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":180708,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J 04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212e0"},"rt":9391,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190166,"subject":"N7ZGQ","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"63040b9d9a587837bd8bd951","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f2"},"rt":36798,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":101468,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM03 PMU 01 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMF F F F K F F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f3"},"rt":13482,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115019,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"G E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f4"},"rt":17656,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132753,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f5"},"rt":7164,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139988,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"U 03 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f6"},"rt":19612,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159669,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"04 PM05 PMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f8"},"rt":15854,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180099,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J J I 11 AM11 AMJ F E G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212f9"},"rt":64563,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244739,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I I F F F F C C Z Z F F C H H H H H O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212fa"},"rt":21134,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266102,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212fb"},"rt":39533,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":305701,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"L L O X B J J J J J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212fc"},"rt":18202,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323971,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"N N Z Z E A K P P M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212fd"},"rt":14326,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338374,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M 01 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212fe"},"rt":6504,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344945,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J F G G G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863212ff"},"rt":11393,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356405,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X O O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321300"},"rt":5263,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361735,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321301"},"rt":14073,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375879,"subject":"EHD8G","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d35a2f3d108309e593b543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M 02 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321313"},"rt":12338,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":234529,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321314"},"rt":15491,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":250068,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"04 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321315"},"rt":14701,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":264817,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A 08 AM09 AMC C C 11 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321316"},"rt":11259,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":276117,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321317"},"rt":6875,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":283143,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AMA I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321319"},"rt":11071,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":295897,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632131a"},"rt":31819,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327761,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J I J J F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632131b"},"rt":56512,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":384321,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B X 03 PMB B 03 PMX O G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632131c"},"rt":66103,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":450460,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4F F B J J J F F M B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632131d"},"rt":26942,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477529,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B J J B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632131e"},"rt":13090,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490662,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"312 PMM M L L L L 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632131f"},"rt":7735,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498442,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G F 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321320"},"rt":12944,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":511445,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3F 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321321"},"rt":7246,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":518744,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321322"},"rt":8491,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":527281,"subject":"D8GCX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d158f6419d2ed0001e2120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321334"},"rt":38857,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":98733,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321335"},"rt":17518,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116313,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I D D 04 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321336"},"rt":45087,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161472,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3C 22C C C C C C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321337"},"rt":54235,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":215798,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"04 PM04 PMD D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321338"},"rt":92152,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":308011,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"6I I A A I H 12 PM05 PMI I I I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632133a"},"rt":19297,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":332392,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"23I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632133b"},"rt":31997,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364456,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"2F F C O O X X O O O O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632133c"},"rt":77149,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441687,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B B X 03 PMB J E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632133d"},"rt":39699,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":481582,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"9B B B E E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632133e"},"rt":10635,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":492282,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632133f"},"rt":12081,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504420,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"C X M M M 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321340"},"rt":10248,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514742,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321341"},"rt":32154,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":546958,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321342"},"rt":18733,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565793,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F X X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321343"},"rt":12937,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":578787,"subject":"AWXGV","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X 02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321355"},"rt":44215,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184363,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM09 AM10 AM12 PM11 AMF F 11 AM11 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321356"},"rt":17602,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":202033,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321357"},"rt":22764,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":224861,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321358"},"rt":32578,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":257521,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM04 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321359"},"rt":49088,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":306672,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F 7J I I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632135b"},"rt":11407,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":344944,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632135c"},"rt":53679,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398687,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"2J H C 5B B B O O O O X N D N X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632135d"},"rt":112990,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":511814,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,J,N","hovered":"B B X J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632135e"},"rt":87921,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":600122,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":"M M M J J J F F M X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632135f"},"rt":6797,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607527,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321360"},"rt":64790,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":672378,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"B B 11 AM12 PMM M L M H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321361"},"rt":27798,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":700396,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321362"},"rt":320932,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1021494,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"X Z F F F F F Z Z Z N N N N X O O F F Z Z O F F C 02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321363"},"rt":75705,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1097455,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM02 PM06 PMX 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321364"},"rt":87963,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1185827,"subject":"K0MZ5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,Z","hovered":"G 03 PMZ Z E 02 PMZ Z Z Z F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321376"},"rt":42522,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":144400,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"12 PM10 AMI O A F F Z Z Z Z U U U F F F F X X D E E G G B B U U Z Z Z Z F F A A C C O O I J H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321377"},"rt":44623,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":189089,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"D D E E D E E 5D E E E G B B B U U U Z F A C C C C O I I I I I H H H J J X Z Z U F F F A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321378"},"rt":32806,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":221958,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"G C C Z U C A F F F K K H H H J J I X D D K K H F F A A Z Z U U U B B B B G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321379"},"rt":69161,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":291181,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"B B B B G U U U Z K K D E E E X F F U Z Z U A A H H H 5J J E E D K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632137a"},"rt":30396,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":321782,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I Z Z U U A C C U I O O I O I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632137c"},"rt":22258,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":346892,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"11 AM01 PMI I I J J X X X O X X O O E E 08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632137d"},"rt":8748,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":355703,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632137e"},"rt":4668,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360438,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632137f"},"rt":2886,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":363396,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321380"},"rt":1393,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364854,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321381"},"rt":2217,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367132,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321382"},"rt":1630,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368825,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321383"},"rt":1359,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370248,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321384"},"rt":1427,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371737,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321385"},"rt":1649,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":373450,"subject":"WTQT8","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6165d57d7256ba57447e76b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321397"},"rt":48257,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132075,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"I I J X H H K O I J A F C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321398"},"rt":14524,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146785,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321399"},"rt":38161,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185036,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632139a"},"rt":16221,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":201349,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"H H H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632139b"},"rt":55200,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":256660,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632139d"},"rt":11796,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":280927,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM1I E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632139e"},"rt":34302,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315318,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C I J F B C M O X X O O X O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632139f"},"rt":47562,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362996,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E F F F F E B G 4X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a0"},"rt":27884,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":390968,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B H H O X J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a1"},"rt":14082,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405140,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4O N N X X F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a2"},"rt":12275,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417505,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a3"},"rt":9087,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426683,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F G G 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a4"},"rt":16847,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":443615,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O G X N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a5"},"rt":7907,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451613,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213a6"},"rt":13299,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465002,"subject":"1HWN9","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"614fe18205aad8c0f76bb0fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213b8"},"rt":64418,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":263954,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMA 11 AMF 11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213b9"},"rt":46172,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":310623,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"Z 12 PM12 PMZ F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213ba"},"rt":19538,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":330380,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AMC C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213bb"},"rt":14168,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":344760,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM04 PMH H I 7U 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213bc"},"rt":62599,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":407549,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"03 PMI I A I I 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213be"},"rt":14204,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":454846,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213bf"},"rt":38052,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":493031,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c0"},"rt":93206,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":586378,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E G X 4403 PMB B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c1"},"rt":77607,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":664236,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B J I I J J J J E E E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c2"},"rt":26300,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":690828,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PMB 3F F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c3"},"rt":13490,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":704468,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c4"},"rt":16288,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720905,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"08 AMB 11 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c5"},"rt":29726,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":750783,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"1F O O Z Z 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c6"},"rt":21724,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":772679,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213c7"},"rt":129027,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":901855,"subject":"7TWDD","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"5699cf0625d9e9000db0c789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X 01 PMJ X X K K 02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213d9"},"rt":32789,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":529821,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213da"},"rt":14237,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":544144,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213db"},"rt":13378,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":557633,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213dc"},"rt":38329,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":596077,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213dd"},"rt":14564,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":610737,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213df"},"rt":8434,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":623130,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e0"},"rt":32081,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":655349,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e1"},"rt":34203,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":689667,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e2"},"rt":27248,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":717009,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e3"},"rt":10696,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":727851,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e4"},"rt":11073,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":739033,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e5"},"rt":8160,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":747300,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e6"},"rt":48187,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":795664,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e7"},"rt":13902,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":809682,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213e8"},"rt":54903,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":864679,"subject":"Q9DH3","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5e437d7404eaba215eafbd2a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213fa"},"rt":51240,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121773,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM08 AMC O C C C C A A I I C C C C C O O J J H H K F F A X X X D D D E B G G K U Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213fb"},"rt":21610,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":143432,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A A K D K C Z Z U Z U B G G E E X J J J H H F A O O C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213fc"},"rt":7824,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151311,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213fd"},"rt":9664,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161032,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"K K H H J J J F F Z Z U Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863213fe"},"rt":10788,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":171874,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321400"},"rt":94769,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270984,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I I I J J E F B B B F F F 02 PMB B B G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321401"},"rt":40110,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311208,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321402"},"rt":72291,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383549,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321403"},"rt":29493,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":413160,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321404"},"rt":8328,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":421534,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321405"},"rt":35999,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457580,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321406"},"rt":9022,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466650,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321407"},"rt":16162,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":482859,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321408"},"rt":5973,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":488881,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321409"},"rt":26510,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515429,"subject":"KHM82","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5b0b4f41641b1200010ecb11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632141b"},"rt":12346,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":28849,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632141c"},"rt":11947,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":40869,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"K O D K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632141d"},"rt":16523,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":57450,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"H C C C C C J C C C F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632141e"},"rt":9684,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":67242,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"9H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632141f"},"rt":8372,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75674,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321421"},"rt":11467,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":90232,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6E E I I I E G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321422"},"rt":35775,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126065,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"E F B F F O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321423"},"rt":28656,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154782,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321424"},"rt":54630,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":209487,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E G G J B B B 3F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321425"},"rt":11884,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221429,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321426"},"rt":11408,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232904,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"4I I 12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321427"},"rt":9894,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242856,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B C F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321428"},"rt":22729,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":265645,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321429"},"rt":6499,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272203,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632142a"},"rt":7984,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280244,"subject":"G86EF","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630563d89f23e3ac8a2142e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632143c"},"rt":54317,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110077,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C A A 11 AMC C C C A F Z U U K K K H J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632143d"},"rt":15951,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":157693,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D K K K C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632143e"},"rt":15502,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173253,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C C F 3G G U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632143f"},"rt":9396,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":182716,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321440"},"rt":8119,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":190910,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321442"},"rt":54408,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":296837,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,B","hovered":"J J I A A B F F F U U U U U Z M Z U D 05 PM06 PM06 PMO I I G G E E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321443"},"rt":82567,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379469,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"12 PM11 AMJ 09 AMB M 12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321444"},"rt":100933,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480765,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"X 03 PMB B X X M X J B F G C C A B B B J J L P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321445"},"rt":65222,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":560436,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X M 09 AMB B 02 PMF F F F J I E B M M E I 11 AM10 AM11 AMI I 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321446"},"rt":21580,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":601965,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PMF F M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321447"},"rt":13183,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":669964,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"J 01 PM12 PM11 AMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321448"},"rt":13348,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":683421,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"O C Z Z F F B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321449"},"rt":10376,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":693916,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G X E E E 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632144a"},"rt":8736,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":702716,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632144b"},"rt":34151,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":795964,"subject":"GQHZH","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d61798f7ad20f001b74922e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM02 PMX J 3X 02 PMX X K 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632145d"},"rt":36047,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178844,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM09 AMC C 09 AM09 AMC C A F F O I H H H F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632145e"},"rt":15181,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":194096,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632145f"},"rt":38409,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":232574,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C 09 AMC C C O O O H B B E B B C 08 AM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321460"},"rt":14408,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":247055,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"J 05 PMH H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321461"},"rt":33314,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":280435,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321463"},"rt":23222,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":311502,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"309 AMI I I J J B B E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321464"},"rt":33363,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344928,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"O O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321465"},"rt":25274,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370269,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321466"},"rt":54905,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":425244,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"6J J J J I J J B B J B E E E I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321467"},"rt":12427,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":437738,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F X A G F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321468"},"rt":15678,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":453480,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"412 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321469"},"rt":12987,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466536,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632146a"},"rt":31527,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498130,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"Z N N Z Z Z Z 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632146b"},"rt":10494,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":508691,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632146c"},"rt":18200,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":526964,"subject":"QJWD6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"630532b3021a956ed55e3333","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632147e"},"rt":19709,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121365,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM10 AMF A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632147f"},"rt":9791,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131288,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321480"},"rt":11527,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142945,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"H C C C C C C A F F 6F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321481"},"rt":15048,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158137,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"404 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321482"},"rt":15412,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173696,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321484"},"rt":23302,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202848,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I 09 AM09 AMI J M M I I I 6E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321485"},"rt":20227,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223205,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"5F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321486"},"rt":41165,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264500,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6E X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321487"},"rt":49086,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313707,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I I 4J J I B B 10 AMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321488"},"rt":12949,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326873,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed86321489"},"rt":10495,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337585,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632148a"},"rt":12174,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349970,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632148b"},"rt":9628,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359811,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"6G Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632148c"},"rt":9734,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369753,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"K 03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632148d"},"rt":17348,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387320,"subject":"4KAPS","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5f1a93900aff791b8c4444f5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed8632149f"},"rt":39435,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97471,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863214a0"},"rt":31083,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":128686,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D 12 PM12 PMZ D D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863214a1"},"rt":15008,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":143825,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863214a2"},"rt":15915,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159944,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PMB B B B B H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c26f72b3ed863214a3"},"rt":24613,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184697,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F,G","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214a5"},"rt":22305,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":210834,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I J J B B C C C 09 AM08 AMI E E E 10 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214a6"},"rt":40020,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251007,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214a7"},"rt":47414,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298550,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214a8"},"rt":28749,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327462,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214a9"},"rt":11938,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339525,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214aa"},"rt":14718,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354592,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ab"},"rt":10878,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365704,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ac"},"rt":27585,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":393468,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"I H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ad"},"rt":7294,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401028,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ae"},"rt":36756,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438069,"subject":"JMH5R","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5fdc18b99bca6f0f95fc120c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N,X","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c0"},"rt":43912,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130688,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AMF A A A A 11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c1"},"rt":9571,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":140496,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"3D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c2"},"rt":14478,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155212,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C C C F 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c3"},"rt":10203,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":165673,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"2H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c4"},"rt":11205,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":177104,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c6"},"rt":14021,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":194749,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I I I I I J 08 AM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c7"},"rt":13853,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208817,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c8"},"rt":80110,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289202,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"B B B B B F F F X X G G G G G B B F C C G G G C 5X O O O X B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214c9"},"rt":39099,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":328564,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B J J E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ca"},"rt":14309,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343086,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214cb"},"rt":12010,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":355349,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214cc"},"rt":20984,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":376587,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"4F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214cd"},"rt":13443,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":390282,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ce"},"rt":7578,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398098,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M 03 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214cf"},"rt":13303,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411497,"subject":"U5DS5","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5aa61dd36475f90001a05dcf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e1"},"rt":34285,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115131,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMA F F Z Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e2"},"rt":20118,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135385,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"2A F K J J D E E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e3"},"rt":9706,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145262,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"2C C F F A 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e4"},"rt":9254,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154661,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e5"},"rt":31670,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186482,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e7"},"rt":8802,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":201561,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e8"},"rt":38294,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240484,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C C C C 10 AMI I F F O O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214e9"},"rt":61798,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":302426,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F B B F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ea"},"rt":38817,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":341992,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214eb"},"rt":8962,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351339,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ec"},"rt":28384,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379885,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ed"},"rt":10085,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390108,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ee"},"rt":12450,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":403058,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214ef"},"rt":10170,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413497,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863214f0"},"rt":13084,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426853,"subject":"ZXKX6","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60430fc782b5752a7ae8d797","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321502"},"rt":28185,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66550,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"J J A A A F F F H H H H Z Z U U U A A J J X I K K K H F F F A F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321503"},"rt":18551,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85174,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"O H D D Z Z Z F F H K J G B X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321504"},"rt":14893,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100140,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"5C C C F F H H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321505"},"rt":9869,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110074,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"K B U U U K H H J F U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321506"},"rt":22117,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132255,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I 02 PM09 AM01 PM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AMA A I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321508"},"rt":32862,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":169444,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I J B B B B F F F B B F F E E 12 PMI 09 AM08 AMF 10 AM03 PMA A G G 12 PM01 PMC H E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321509"},"rt":24714,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194227,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C 10 AMB 11 AMF M X X X X X O X J O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632150a"},"rt":21776,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216068,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E E B F F E G G 5F G G 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632150b"},"rt":23950,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":240086,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B F I E I I M M I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632150c"},"rt":19060,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259218,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E F 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632150d"},"rt":6479,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265761,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632150e"},"rt":15396,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281240,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632150f"},"rt":12754,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":294071,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321510"},"rt":7356,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301487,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X 03 PM04 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321511"},"rt":19945,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321498,"subject":"QDXOK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"615b22b2b654b57bcb5ad7b3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"B B B F B B B 12 PMJ J 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321523"},"rt":53869,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142095,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"310 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMC C F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321524"},"rt":22942,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":165073,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,E","hovered":"D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321525"},"rt":11129,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":176234,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321526"},"rt":31894,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208166,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,B","hovered":"F F F 4F 03 PM04 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321527"},"rt":30268,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":238467,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321529"},"rt":84536,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327974,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"K K K 02 PM02 PMK K K K J I E E F B B F X O C C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632152a"},"rt":37859,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365920,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"E C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632152b"},"rt":31123,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397080,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632152c"},"rt":20644,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":417776,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632152d"},"rt":7786,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425655,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F 03 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632152e"},"rt":10606,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436296,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632152f"},"rt":12515,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448844,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321530"},"rt":19216,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":468094,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"7Z X X O Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321531"},"rt":13661,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481787,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PM04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321532"},"rt":19333,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501152,"subject":"B4TKK","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"61075af85969d97b256603cc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AM01 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321544"},"rt":21057,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":69442,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"C F 03 PM04 PM05 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM11 AM11 AMO O I C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321545"},"rt":14659,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84223,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,E","hovered":"G G H D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321546"},"rt":17734,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":102050,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM11 AMZ C C C A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321547"},"rt":43963,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146088,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"09 AM10 AME E E E G G B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321548"},"rt":27652,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173830,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C I I I O A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632154a"},"rt":19107,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":196309,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"J C K K K K O O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632154b"},"rt":20002,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216395,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,X","hovered":"I M M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632154c"},"rt":23397,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240073,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"F B B X X 03 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632154d"},"rt":16331,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256464,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632154e"},"rt":11174,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267721,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z Z F F B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632154f"},"rt":12151,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279962,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F B F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321550"},"rt":9072,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289107,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321551"},"rt":19454,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":308647,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"O O Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321552"},"rt":9794,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":318532,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321553"},"rt":44668,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363260,"subject":"PBY6J","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"60a2cee2b59ef2c89c0b388a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321565"},"rt":16973,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94970,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMA A 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321566"},"rt":133774,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":228856,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,E","hovered":"D D D D D D D 12 PM12 PMF F F F F H H H F F D E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321567"},"rt":37807,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":267061,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C A F F F F F F F G F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321568"},"rt":23511,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":290680,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"3G G U U U U U F H K K H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321569"},"rt":87032,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":377821,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,H","hovered":"A A A F F A A A X J J D J J I H I H H H H H H K I I I O O I H H I H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632156b"},"rt":122033,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506895,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,D,I","hovered":"08 AMK K K K K A A J J B O B O I B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632156c"},"rt":66374,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":573576,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632156d"},"rt":260427,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":834400,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,J,N","hovered":"K K K B B I E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632156e"},"rt":62529,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":897332,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632156f"},"rt":29685,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":927419,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,C,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321570"},"rt":29975,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":957499,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,G,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321571"},"rt":63735,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1021335,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,C,O","hovered":"F C C F G F F G G C F G F F F C B C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321572"},"rt":44870,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1066599,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N,X","hovered":"C Z Z Z Z H H Z Z Z O X O H H Z N N X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321573"},"rt":69166,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1135869,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,G,O","hovered":"12 PM01 PM03 PM03 PMH H C C L G B B C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321574"},"rt":37745,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1173920,"subject":"9VJ83","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"5d17227bab610c00170fd98d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321586"},"rt":44599,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105114,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AM22A F 2C C C C 01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AMF F F F A A A A A O U Z Z U H H H J J D D 01 PMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321587"},"rt":17437,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122607,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"11 AM12 PMO Z U D D F A K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321588"},"rt":20557,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":143224,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM01 PMF H C C F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321589"},"rt":10156,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153433,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"05 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PMB B B H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632158a"},"rt":32426,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185917,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"02 PMU I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632158c"},"rt":34845,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":225018,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"J I I I I I I J J B B F F A A G 2M M M M M M M M 09 AM08 AMI 09 AM10 AM11 AMF F 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMC C 11 AMC 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632158d"},"rt":110921,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335991,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"M B B B B B F F F B F F 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMX O N N X 666J F X X X O O O X X X O O O O X X X O O H O O X O 11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632158e"},"rt":52091,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388278,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed8632158f"},"rt":43825,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":432154,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O B N M J J J J I I I 11 AMJ J F B E E E E F B B I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321590"},"rt":16038,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448245,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 PM03 PM02 PMZ C F 02 PMF E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321591"},"rt":11882,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460184,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM11 AM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321592"},"rt":6627,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466865,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321593"},"rt":20847,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487763,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M M 3Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321594"},"rt":6415,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":494235,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed86321595"},"rt":16112,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510399,"subject":"FO3RX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62f6a5e7bd056277be777c68","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AM05 PMX X X K O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215a7"},"rt":28309,"condition":"221","q":1,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76103,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215a8"},"rt":17490,"condition":"221","q":2,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":93694,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215a9"},"rt":20480,"condition":"221","q":3,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":114260,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215aa"},"rt":10969,"condition":"221","q":4,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125316,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"6K 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ab"},"rt":25799,"condition":"221","q":5,"explicit":"2","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151201,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ad"},"rt":12031,"condition":"221","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167434,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ae"},"rt":17694,"condition":"221","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185219,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215af"},"rt":37426,"condition":"221","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":222913,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7C C B B F F G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b0"},"rt":29223,"condition":"221","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":252221,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM3I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b1"},"rt":22240,"condition":"221","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274547,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B Z O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b2"},"rt":8779,"condition":"221","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283414,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM02 PM10 AM012 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b3"},"rt":3162,"condition":"221","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286665,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b4"},"rt":19924,"condition":"221","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":306675,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"5F H Z Z O O X B X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b5"},"rt":17562,"condition":"221","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324328,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I X X B B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215b6"},"rt":24338,"condition":"221","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348753,"subject":"LYNWR","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630575e5f8bc88efe44ef98c","sona_id":"62d24fc11889482bc5b71965","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"M 288A L L K X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215c8"},"rt":51290,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115290,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AMO O C C C F K 5O H H A A F F F X X X J J D D E E B B B G A U F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215c9"},"rt":23847,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139232,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D K K 5D D Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ca"},"rt":12409,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151731,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215cb"},"rt":12807,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164647,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PMH H H H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215cc"},"rt":38961,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203696,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A A A A I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ce"},"rt":11317,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":220622,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12A A A A E E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215cf"},"rt":64211,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284923,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F B B J 08 AM10 AMF F C 01 PMX O M X X O 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d0"},"rt":121504,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406644,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B F F B B 10 AMG C F A G G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d1"},"rt":58665,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":465508,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F B I I J 0E F B B B J 09 AM08 AMI I I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d2"},"rt":13139,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":478749,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d3"},"rt":11732,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490573,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M L L L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d4"},"rt":10677,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501326,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J F F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d5"},"rt":13230,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":514627,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3O Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d6"},"rt":11440,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":526156,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215d7"},"rt":27883,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554125,"subject":"GY0YU","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"6107f318a5a3d70640835aea","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"7J 01 PM02 PM02 PMX X X X X X X 02 PMX X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215e9"},"rt":85382,"condition":"321","q":1,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":141898,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM03 PM06 PM07 PM06 PM11 AM11 AM11 AMO O O O 11 AM11 AM09 AM08 AMO O C C C C A F U F Z Z Z U U O I I I H H H J J D E E K K K K U U Z Z Z Z U G G G G B B B B B H H H H H H H A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ea"},"rt":65305,"condition":"321","q":2,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":207857,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"H D Z Z Z Z Z U U Z F F A C C O O I I I I I H H H K K K X X X D D D E E E G G G B K K K K K K H H F F F F A A A C C Z Z Z O I H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215eb"},"rt":44524,"condition":"321","q":3,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":253004,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K C C C C C C C A F U U Z U B B B G G K K K K O O O E H H I J D D D D D X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ec"},"rt":47393,"condition":"321","q":4,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":300878,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"B B B G G E K U U Z Z Z F A A C C C C C O O O I H H H J D K K K K K K K K E E E E E E D D X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ed"},"rt":70654,"condition":"321","q":5,"explicit":"3","impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":372185,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U Z Z H I H H I J J J J I I O O O O I I C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215ef"},"rt":52002,"condition":"321","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":431560,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J J I I I I I I I I J O J J J J J I I M X O I I I I 008 AMJ I J I E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f0"},"rt":33974,"condition":"321","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465995,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E C 12 PM11 AMJ J J B B B B B F F B B B F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f1"},"rt":42810,"condition":"321","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":509335,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J,M","hovered":"G C 6B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f2"},"rt":31339,"condition":"321","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":541127,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"5F J I I I J E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f3"},"rt":69197,"condition":"321","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":611334,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,I,J,M","hovered":"B I J J J I J J J J J J F F F F B M 01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMM M M M 01 PM01 PM01 PMM M M M 02 PM01 PMB F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f4"},"rt":20460,"condition":"321","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":632680,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMM B B B B F M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f5"},"rt":26051,"condition":"321","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":659190,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"6H H C F F F 12 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f6"},"rt":25917,"condition":"321","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":685617,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,O","hovered":"N O Z Z Z O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f7"},"rt":14061,"condition":"321","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":701808,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X 03 PMX X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6305a3c36f72b3ed863215f8"},"rt":65095,"condition":"321","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767519,"subject":"JJPDX","study":"SGC3B","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305833e06c2929ccd50f4b9","sona_id":"62962c18b210880e85c1fc8e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"C 12 PMM C C C B B G 02 PM02 PMC C G C C G G C C O O C C B M 04 PMC H C C C 2"}]
